[
  {
    "id": "508",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "IAM roles are global, not associated with any region?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["true"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "509",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You can't attach an IAM roles to a running EC2 instance?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["false"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "510",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "IAM",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "You can attach an IAM roles to a running EC2 instance using which?",
      "answers": [
        "cli",
        "console",
        "CloudWatch",
        "CloudFormation",
        "Auto Scaling Groups"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["cli", "console"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "511",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "The url to get meta-data for an EC2 instance is used as such: as such http://___.___.___.___/_____/________?",
      "answers": [
        "169.254.169.254/latest/meta-data/",
        "254.169.254.169/latest/meta-data/",
        "169.254.169.254/meta-data/latest/",
        "254.169.254.169/meta-data/latest/",
        "169.254.169.254/meta-data/"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["169.254.169.254/latest/meta-data/"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "512",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "An EC2 placement group is which?",
      "answers": [
        "a logical grouping of instances within a single AZ",
        "a logical grouping of instances spread across multiple AZs",
        "a physical group of instances within a single AZ",
        "a physical group of instances spread across multiple AZs",
        "a logical group of instances behind a load balancer and an auto-scaling group"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["a logical grouping of instances within a single AZ"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "513",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Using EC2 placement groups enables _______?",
      "answers": [
        "applications to participate in a low latency, 10 Gbps network",
        "applications to spread their workload across multiple AZs using a load balancer",
        "application to place specific components on selected EC2 instances",
        "applications to run in multiple regions"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["applications to participate in a low latency, 10 Gbps network"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "514",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "EC2 placement groups are recommended for _______?",
      "answers": [
        "applications that benefit from low network latency",
        "applications that benefit from high network throughput",
        "applications that benefit from both low network latency and high network throughput",
        "applications that benefit from speed covering great distances"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["applications that benefit from both low network latency and high network throughput"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "515",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "Use cases for EC2 placement groups include _______?",
      "answers": [
        "Hadoop clusters",
        "Casandra back-end databases",
        "DynamoDB database tables",
        "Aurora database instances",
        "Kubernetes clusters"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Hadoop clusters", "Casandra back-end databases"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "516",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "An EC2 placement group can span multiple AZs?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["false"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "517",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "The name you specify for your EC2 placement group must be unique within ________?",
      "answers": [
        "your AWS account",
        "its region",
        "the global namespace",
        "its AZ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["your AWS account"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "518",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 4",
      "question": "Only these types of EC2 instances can be launched with an EC2 placement group?",
      "answers": [
        "Compute Optimized",
        "GPU (P2)",
        "Memory Optimized",
        "Storage Optimized",
        "Graphics Intensive",
        "General Purpose",
        "Dense Storage",
        "Field Programmable"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Compute Optimized", "GPU", "Memory Optimized", "Storage Optimized"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "519",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "AWS recommends _________ EC2 instances within placement groups?",
      "answers": [
        "homogeneous",
        "heterogeneous",
        "large",
        "contemporaneous"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["homogeneous"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "520",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "AWS recommends homogeneous EC2 instances within placement groups, meaning _________?",
      "answers": [
        "same size and same family",
        "same family",
        "same size",
        "same configuration"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["same size and same family"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "521",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You can merge EC2 placement groups?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["false"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "522",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You can move an existing EC2 instance into a placement group?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["false"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "523",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "To move an existing EC2 instance into a placement group you can do which?",
      "answers": [
        "create an AMI from the existing EC2 instance, then launch a new instance from the AMI into a placement group",
        "launch the existing instance into a plcaement group",
        "create a snapshot of the existing EC2 instance's root volume, then launch the instace from the snapshot into the placement group",
        "you can't move an existing EC2 instance into a placement group using any of these techniques"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["create an AMI from the existing EC2 instance, then launch a new instance from the AMI into a placement group"]
    }
  }
]
